So, we've created an XGBoost model and it's
我们创建了一个 XGBoost 模型
deployed and being used somewhere in an application.
并将模型部署到了应用中
But, it turns out that for some reason,
但是因为某种原因
our XGBoost model is too complicated.
该 XGBoost 模型太复杂
Maybe it's taking up too many resources at inference time or
也许在推理时占用太多资源
we're just having to use it too often or
或者我们需要多次使用它
maybe we can't explain the way it works very well.
或者我们无法很好地解释它的运行原理
So, what we'd really like,
所以我们非常希望
is a much simpler model that we can explain.
有一个能解释的更简单模型
In any case, suppose that now what we'd like to do is create a linear model.
无论是何种情况 都假设现在我们想创建一个线性模型
We can create a linear model in much the same way as we created an XGBoost model.
创建线性模型的方式与创建 XGBoost 模型的很相似
We will start by using the high-level approach to create the model artifacts,
先通过高阶方法创建模型工件
which can be done by first creating an estimator object,
首先创建一个 estimator 对象
making sure that the container that we use during training is
确保在训练过程中使用的容器是
the linear learner container and just like in the XGBoost case,
linear-learner 容器 和 XGBoost 模型一样
we need to set some hyperparameters specific to this algorithm.
我们需要设定特定于此算法的超参数
In this case our data has 13 features and
数据有 13 个特征
so we need to make sure to set the feature dimension to 13.
所以需要将特征维数设为 13
We are doing a regression because we are trying to
我们将使用回归 因为要预测实数
estimate a real number and the Linear Learner algorithm,
linear-learner 算法
while creating a linear model,
在创建线性模型时
does so by looking at mini-batches.
将采用迷你批次
In particular it uses the Gradient Descent Algorithm in order to fit the model.
它会使用梯度下降法拟合模型
So, we can set here the number of rows that are used in each mini-batch.
我们可以在这里设定每个迷你批次的行数
Once we've set the hyperparameters,
设置了超参数后
we can then call the fit method and SageMaker will take care of
调用 fit() 方法
creating the model artifacts for our linear learner model.
SageMaker 将为线性模型创建模型工件
Now, that we've finished fitting our linear model,
拟合了线性模型后
we can go ahead and deploy that model
我们将部署模型
much in the same way as we did with the XGBoost model.
方式与部署 XGBoost 模型的几乎一样
First, we create a model object inside of SageMaker by describing where
首先在 SageMaker 中创建一个模型对象
the model artifacts are being stored and
指定模型工件的存储位置
which container should be used to perform inference.
以及推理用到的容器
Once that's done, we can create an endpoint configuration.
然后创建端点配置
Much like the XGBoost example,
与 XGBoost 示例一样,
we have only a single production variant and
我们只有一个生产变体
we call that production variant the linear model.
称之为 Linear-Model
Now, that we have an endpoint configuration that uses our newly trained model,
创建了使用新训练的模型的端点配置后
we can ask SageMaker to create an endpoint with those properties.
我们可以要求 SageMaker 使用这些属性创建一个端点
Once our endpoint has been set up,
设置好端点后
we can go ahead and try and test here our model to make
我们可以测试模型
sure that everything is working the way we expect it to.
看看一切是否都按预期运行
Just like with the XGBoost endpoint,
与 XGBoost 端点一样
we're going to send the first row of our test data,
我们将发送第一行测试数据
which we do by first serializing it and then sending it off
首先序列化数据 然后发送给端点
to our endpoint and just like in the XGBoost case,
与 XGBoost 示例一样
we get a JSON object as a response,
获得的响应是 JSON 对象
which in this case it tells us that our return type is
告诉我们返回类型是 JSON 数据
JSON data and that the variant that was used was the linear model.
使用的变体是 Linear-Model
Of course, we expect that the variant used was
当然 使用的变体肯定是 Linear-Model
a linear model since we only have one production variant listed.
因为我们仅列出了一个生产变体
So now, if we read in the body object and turn it back into a string,
下面读取 body 对象并转换成字符串
what we get as described in the response variable is a JSON return.
正如 response 变量所描述的 我们获得的返回内容是 JSON 数据
In this case, it is a JSON object,
是一个 JSON 对象
which contains the score of 35.8.
其中包含分数 35.8
So, if we compare that again with the true value,
将这个分数与真实值进行比较
we can see that in this particular case
可以看到 对于这个分数来说
the linear model is actually doing a little bit better than our XGBoost model.
线性模型比 XGBoost 模型的效果稍微好些
Of course, looking at a single data point is not
当然 只查看一个数据点
a very good way of determining how good a model is behaving,
并不能很好地判断模型的行为效果
but it at least gives us something to look at.
但是至少也是一项数据
Next, since we're not going to use the linear model all by itself,
接下来 因为我们并不单独使用线性模型
we're going to shut down the endpoint.
所以将关闭端点